Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
The search for true love
is never easy
and for some.
dating has been a disaster.
# ZOMBIES: Time Of The Season
(SCREAMS)
Oh. you meant
that kind of role-play!
Get out!
She'll love that red wine.
But their luck is about to change.
(BEEPING)
(BELL RINGS)
Phone first.
Paradise is waiting.
And the games are about to begin.
Get ready for the ultimate
summer of love.
Welcome to paradise.
where 11 sexy singles are about to
experience
a summer they'll never forget.
Even if some of them want to.
And it is all going to happen right
here in the Love Island villa.
And makeover alert!
This year the producers have
splashed the cash on brand-new beds
and a fancy sofa. plus the last
word in luxury:
some pretend grass on a wall.
Classy!
Remember. in this place.
there is one golden rule.
To be there at the finish
and have a shot at that 50 grand.
you have got to couple up
or clear out.
The villa's ready.
cue those sexy singles!
Woo-hoo!
Oh. my God!
Yes!
Oh. my God. Oh. my gosh. hi.
I'm Hayley. Nice to meet you.
Lord.  It looks amazing.
Look how big it is.
Oh. we are actually living here!
It is unreal. We are going to have
the summer of our lives!
Oh. my gosh.
I'm Samira. 22 from London and
I'm a musical theatre performer.
I can sing. I can dance. I can act.
# I'm lookin' for something. baby #
I have performed in Mamma Mia
and Dreamgirls in the West End.
I'm your dream girl. (LAUGHS)
Oh. my God. I'm going to get slated
for this.
My ex-boyfriend broke my heart.
Being dumped made my heart
go to stone.
I was like a cold bitch.
Now it has been two years nearly.
I'm starting to trust people
a lot more.
I am so excited
to get in the villa.
I am a boy-crazy girl.
I do love a bit of a flirt.
My perfect guy would have
dark hair.
think Zac Efron. that smouldering
look.
Nice face tan. That's all it is.
When I see a fit boy.
I'm like. aaah!
Like. mmm!
See. how good was that?
Er... er...
(CORK POPS) Wahey!
This is insane. Let's do it this
way. Let's do yours first.
Was you so nervous this morning?
It was the worst sleep of my life.
Oh. my gosh. the worst sleep ever.
Cheers.  Oh. my gosh. it's going
to bubble over.
Cheers!  Cheers! Woo!
I know a word in Spanish. Gambas.
That's prawns. That all I know.
I'm Hayley Hughes. 21 and a model
from Liverpool.
I'm cute. funny. feisty. dozy...
Can I say that?
The biggest word I've ever used
is...
I don't really know.
I don't really use big words.
I've been single now
for six months.
I was in a relationship
for five years.
He cheated on me numerous times.
Disgusting.
I don't like a guy who just wants
to have his willy up
as many girls as he wants.
Boy-bye.
I've only slept with one person.
Nowadays. girls have slept
with loads. haven't they?
Maybe I just need to experience
a bit more. Who knows?
Oh. my gosh.  It is unreal.
I can't get over it.
I simply can't. You know when
you're just like. I like the view.
That view is amazing.
We are going to be waking up to
that every morning.  Absolutely
stunning.
This is unreal.
Oh!
Oh. my God!  Hi!
I'm Samira. Nice to meet you.
I'm Hayley. Really nice to meet
you.  I'm Kendall.  How are you?
I'm all right.  Are you nervous?
I'm so excited.
Have some champagne.
We'll do like 5.000 cheerses.
Honestly. I'm so nervous.
but excited.
I thought I was going to wee.
I'm Kendall. 26 from sunny
Blackpool.
I'm currently a manager
at a shoe shop.
33% discount. so it's pretty good.
I've been single for seven months.
That is due to my ex-fiance of five
years leaving me last year.
He just woke up one morning and
said. "I don't love you any more".
Obviously. it hurt like hell.
Being out of the dating game for
about six years.
there is so much to learn!
I am open to anything.
That sounds awful!
No. not open to anything!
But you know what I mean.
The things I'm looking for are
someone quite down to earth.
Hopefully he will just like me
for me.
I'm not going to try to pretend
to be somebody that I'm not.
If he likes me. he likes me. so...
Maybe I shouldn't have swore.
So what's your type?
Erm. I go for tall. dark
and handsome.
Every girl says that!
I just want someone where you wake
up and think. "You're fit".
First thing in the morning.
What do you do for work?  Modelling.
Model. And you?
I work at a shoe shop.
Do you?  Amazing.  What do you do?
Dancer.
Can you twerk?
No. I can't.
Same. I just need a big booty.
Woo. woo. woo. woo!
Oh. my God. I'm so excited!
Hi!
(SCREAMS) Hello!
Hello. I'm Dani.
Oh. my God. this is amazing.
I'm Samira. Nice to meet you.
You all look amazing.
You look so cool. I'm shaking.
Have some champagne. I'm Kendall.
Like Kendall Jenner!
I'm Dani. I'm 21. I'm from Essex
and I work as a barmaid.
Life as a barmaid is fun.
I'm actually really good
at pulling a pint.
You have to make sure it's got
the perfect head on it
because they get
the hump otherwise.
I've been single now for nearly
two years. cos I just have no luck.
I just go for boys that sell me
a dream and I believe the dream
and I end up crying
at the end of it.
My friends are like.
"Dani. we told you so."
My dad is happy now that
I'm on Love Island.
When I first told him. he wasn't
ecstatic.
I have got to find a boyfriend.
I am ready for love. and he's going
to have to live with it.
I can't wait to get in the villa
and I can't wait to meet the boys.
Hopefully I do find the love of my
life.
Romeo. Romeo.
where art thou. Romeo?
What's your type?
I never have the same exes.
You go for what you like.
Yeah. it is always chat for me.
How long have you been single for?
About eight months. I was engaged
last year.
(GASPS)  What?!
Oh. my God.
OK. well. this is the perfect place
to get over that.
It is just annoying that you can't
force someone to love you.
isn't it?
Was your heart broken?
Yeah.
Let's hug it out.
I'm so hot. I'm like...
Woo-hoo!
Hello!
Another girl. another girl!
Hey!  You look lovely.
Are you OK?
I love your accent.
Lovely to meet you.  I'm Laura.
We are all so brown.
I thought I put a bit too much
fake tan on!
No. we are fine.
I'm Laura and I'm an air hostess
from Scotland.
I'm a hostess with the mostess!
Life as cabin crew is never
a dull moment.
Yes. I'm a fully-fledged member
of the mile-high club.
Like. welcome. Everyone. join me!
I've been single
for about three months.
My friends make fun of me. I've
literally had about nine boyfriends.
Boyfriend number one.
we went to school together.
Boyfriend number two. he was
actually my friend's boyfriend.
Oh. that's so bad.
Number three. he was insane.
Number four. I was. like.
obsessed...
..number six.
he played international rugby.
I think he married the girl he
cheated on me with...
..and number nine. cheated on me.
I think I'm a good catch.
They are all just crazy.
Find me a husband. please.
How long have you been single for?
Not that long.
Maybe two or three months.
We are all fresh.  Why did that end?
Er. oh... Dear God!
It wasn't bad but. yeah.
he cheated on me.
But we are still friends.
Did he know you were coming
on the show?
Well. he does now!
(LAUGHTER)
So the ladies have landed.
I think it is time we add some men
to the mix.
And I know just the person to do it.
Brace yourself. Britain.
it's the return of the Flack.
Here comes Caroline!
(CHEERING)
You all look incredible.
Are we in the mood for love?
Yes!
Let's have a little chat
about boys.
Because that is why we're here.
right?
Yes. Where are they? (LAUGHTER)
They'll be here soon!
Wait. wait. wait.
Let's see your ring!
There you go.
That feels different this time!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
So excited.  I am so nervous.
OK. let's chat love.
Are we here for love or lust?
I think I'm here for love.
I think. in past things.
it has always just been lust.
I want to have a proper connection
and get to know someone.
You want to find the real thing.
Yeah. I'm bored of all of that.
A bit of lust is fine. but we don't
want it all our lives. do we?
I'm here for love.
Good.
Describe for me your ideal guy.
Tall. dark and handsome. I think
every girl says that. don't they?
But I want someone
that makes me laugh.
I can't sit there with someone
who is just boring.
So we don't want any boring people?
No.
I like a pretty boy.  Do you?
Yes. I love the boy-next-door
kind of boy.
Has anyone got a game plan?
To make the boys love me.
(LAUGHTER)
And how do you do that. Laura?
Because I'm super fun.
Do you make them laugh?
Yes. of course.
I get the best outfits
and workout.
Ladies. let's not waste
any more time.
Want to meet some boys?
ALL: YES!  Come on. then.
Good luck. girls.
Girls. it is time to couple up.
The boys will come in one by one
and I'm going to ask you to
step forward if you fancy them.
The boy will then decide which girl
he wants to couple up with.
Are we ready to meet our first boy?
Yes!
OK. everybody. this is Niall.
Woo!
You all right. girls?
Hi!
What's everyone saying?
He's so cute!
Am I looking good? I don't want
to look like a catfish though.
I look proper good on my Insta.
I'm Niall. I'm 23. I'm a student
from Coventry.
I love Harry Potter.
I've got Hermione Granger's wand
tattooed on my forearm.
I guess if girl is lucky
after a night out.
she can come back and see my wand!
When I was younger. honestly.
I was really ugly.
I used to have really sticky-out
ears.
About a year ago.
I got them pinned back.
I used to be a beanpole
with big ears.
I never got any female attention.
When a girl sees me.
they probably think
I'm a typical low-cut.
muscle-fit lad.
Once they get to know me.
hopefully they will get to realise
I've got loads of layers.
a bit like an onion.
I think the meaning of love. it is
a feeling when you are with a girl.
she's probably not got
a lot of make-up on.
wearing some grey trackies and not
looking her best.
And in that moment. you are looking
at her and you think.
"You know what? I love you!"
and that's it.
Welcome to Love Island.  Nice
to have me. Does that make sense?
No.  Does it not?
It is nice to have you.  Thank you.
What is going through your mind?
I don't think I've ever seen girls
this fit in real life.
It is like girls on Instagram.
but they actually look like
they do in person.
Everyone is looking mad.
What you see is what you get. yeah?
Yeah.
As you know. Love Island is all
about finding your perfect match.
This is your first very important
decision.
Which girl you want
to couple up with.
I'm going to make your decision
a little bit easier.
I'm going to ask the girls to step
forward if they fancy you.
OK. girls. if you like the look of
Niall. then please step forward.
The coupling up is underway.
but who's going to step forward
for Niall?
OK. girls. if you like the look
of Niall. then kindly step forward.
Oh. Kendall. why did you step
forward?
He just seems really happy and
outgoing and funny.
Hayley. why didn't you
step forward?
He seems a nice guy.
but just not my type.
I'm more of an investment
for the future.
With me. I haven't hit my peak yet.
so give me five years...
Obviously then. I'm sorted. isn't
it?
Dani. why didn't you step forward?
I just. I don't know. I can't work
it out.  I'm mysterious.
That's what it is.
Kendall has stepped forward
for you.
However this is your first
very important decision.
You can choose any of these girls
to couple up with.
Which girl would you like
to couple up with. Niall?
Kendall.
Off you go. Gorgeous!
Aw!
We have our first Love Island
couple of 2018: Kendall and Niall!
How are you feeling. Niall?
I am feeling happy with myself.
You're absolutely beautiful.
OK. are we ready for
our second boy?
ALL: Yes.
Let's meet Alex.
Hello. everyone.
ALL: Hello.
I'm Alex. I'm 27.
I'm an A&E doctor.
I am five hours into a pretty busy
A&E shift.
Life at the doctors is very fast
pace.
One minute you are dealing with a
cut fingernail
to a full-blown cardiac arrest.
A&E is going to be very different
to Love Island.
I'm always on standby
though to mend any broken hearts.
When my work people see this...
Sometimes at work. I have patients
flirting with me.
some young. some old.
So obviously my bedside manner's
quite professional at work
but my bedside manner out of work...
I've been single for about three
years
so I'm definitely looking for
love now.
I'm 27 years old. mum's nagging me.
telling me need to find someone
so I think it is about time.
Welcome to Love Island.
Thank you.
How are you feeling?
A little bit nervous.
It's good to be nervous. That's
healthy.  I think so yeah.
You're about to couple up with one
of these gorgeous girls.
They are beautiful.  Before you
decide who you couple up with.
I'm going to make it a little bit
easier for you.
I'm going to ask the girls to step
forward if they fancy you.
No pressure. girls.
Girls. if you fancy Alex. please
step forward.
Ah!
Girls. this is shocking. Laura
why've you not stepped forward?
I feel so bad.
I usually prefer. like. darker.
Can you grow a beard?
A little bit. yeah.
a bit of a goatee or something.
I can work on it.
I can see stubble.
Hayley.
why did you not step forward?
I don't know.  OK. What's he missing
that you usually go for?
I don't know. the tan maybe.
Alex. do you go a nice brown?
I think so. yes.
OK. so he can tan Hayley.
that can happen.
We'll see in a few weeks. then.
(LAUGHTER)
OK. well. Alex. it doesn't matter.
You can couple up with any of the
girls including Kendall.
Which girl would you like
to couple up with today?
Um.
I think I can grow the goatee the
quickest so I'll start on the end.
Yay. Laura!
Congratulations.
Alex. go and see Laura.
I do fancy you. I was joking.
Ah. that's good.
Laura. how are you feeling?
Yeah. good.
I'm very excited. this is going to
be great.
Samira. why have you not stepped
forward yet?
I'm not sure. I think. your
personality was fantastic.
I kind of
wish I did step forward now.
Who for?
Regrets already.
Kendall.
I'll grip him a little tighter.
Wow.
Shall we meet boy number three?
ALL: Yes!
This is Wes.
Oh.
Abs.
Caroline. you've done it again.
What have I done?
All of these gorgeous girls again.
I'm Wes. I'm 20 years old. I'm a
design-age engineer in nuclear...
I'm a nuclear... I'm Wes.
I'm a design engineer in the
electrical and nuclear industry.
Why couldn't I do that before?
Obviously. my job role is a massive
help
when you're trying to graft girls.
They instantaneously think I'm
intelligent.
I can definitely engineer the ride
of someone's life.
I've got the gears
and the gearstick to do it as well.
I just thought of that on the spot.
I am definitely a romantic guy.
I love treating girls the way they
are supposed to be treated. like
queens.
It's the way I've been brought up.
In the villa there's no competition
for me. everybody's fair game.
I'm always gonna walk out with the
girl of my dreams. no matter what.
Welcome to Love Island. Wes.
How are you feeling?  Good. excited.
We've already got two couples as
you can see. Kendall and Niall.
We've got to Laura and Alex.
And we've got three hot single
ladies left.
Hayley. Samira and Dani.  OK.
OK. ladies. if you like the look of
Wes. step forward.
I mean. look at that eight-pack.
guys.
Laura's stepped forward.
It's one of them.
Why have you stepped forward. why
have you left dear old Alex behind?
Oh. gosh. I don't know. he's got
loads of packs.
He's got an eight-pack.
He's got like a 20-pack.
He seems really sweet.
I like your accent.
Thank you.
Alex. how does that make you feel?
It's not been the best start but it
can get better.
Dani. why didn't you step forward?
I don't know. like. usually I think
I'm going to walk in
and look at them and fall in love.
but it's not going to happen is it?
I need to get to know them.  I'm
really sorry.
Don't worry.
Wes. this decision is completely
down to you.
You are in control. you can choose
any girl standing in front of you.
but which girl would you like to
couple up with?
I'm going to have to stick with
Laura.
You're going to choose Laura.
congratulations.  Sorry. man.
Alex. we're going to have to pull
you over here to the subs bench.
Congratulations. guys.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Alex. Wes has stolen your girl.
which means
you are going to be on the subs
bench until the next two boys
have chosen their girls.
Are you all right?  Yup.
You can pick up some sun.  Exactly.
I'm picking up that tan.
Laura. are you happy?
Yes. I don't even mind the sweat.
You don't mind it!
OK. you three hot single girls.
none of you have stepped forward.
What are you waiting for?
I'm being a bit picky to be honest.
this is really bad of me.
I'm being very picky.
OK. when I think it's time we meet
boy number four.
Everybody meet Eyal.
Hello.
His hair is cool.
I am Eyal.
I'm 22 and I'm from London and I'm
a model.
I would like to think I'm not a
typical model.
I am quite a spiritual person.
Yeah. I do feel like I inspire
people.
I try and show the truth about life
and my life.
My aura and energy is just a
happy-go-lucky person.
Someone that doesn't take life too
seriously.
I've got to have someone that has
some depth to them
and I also like someone that likes
to have fun in the bedroom
and cracks the whip every now and
again.
Literally and metaphorically.
Hello. everyone.
You all look beautiful.
Look at you.
having a good scan there.
I am indeed.  Are you all right?  I'm
good. how are you?
Good thank you. Welcome to Love
Island.
OK. Eyal. you have to decide who
you want to couple up with.
I am going to make it a little bit
easier for you.
so. girls. if you fancy Eyal.
step forward.
(LAUGHTER)
So this is what you've all been
waiting for.
OK.
Thank you.
He is very happy.  I am.
Hayley. why did you step forward?
I think those red shorts work.
Sweet.
Fair enough.
And I like his hair.  Thanks.
Samira. why did you step forward?
The same reason. you've got really
cool hair. Nice to play with.
To run your fingers through.  Run my
fingers through your hair.
And. Dani?  Yeah I just like the
look of you. you seem really sweet.
I like your voice as well.
OK. Eyal. which girl would you
like to couple up with?
I'm going to go with Hayley.
Congratulations.
How are you?  Thank you.
Samira. how are you feeling?
I'm actually OK.
You are better than you thought you
would be?  I'm fine.
OK. good. Dani?
Yeah fine. Like. I'm fine. It's all
right. it is what it is.
The good news for Alex. whoever
doesn't couple up with
the next boy. couples up with you.
OK.
Let's meet Jack.
How are we doing. all right?
We're all right.
Nerve-racking this. isn't it?
I'm Jack. I'm 26
and I sell pens for a living.
I 100% have got
the gift of the gab.
Hello. Judy. how are you? All the
better now I've spoken to you.
Straight away with a joke.
they love it.
This pen is going to change your
life.
You can write in the dark with it
and it will make you feel good
about yourself.
I'll send three down to you.
I make stationery fun.
I love being well-groomed.
I absolutely love my pearly whites.
I went all the way to Turkey to get
these.
I came back with a winning smile
and a nice little holiday.
I don't know if I've been in love
before. my mum's always said.
when you find the person you love
and you just instantly know.
My mum's always right so hopefully
I'll fall in love in the villa
and it can be like a proper love
story.
Jack. welcome to Love Island.  Thank
you.
What's going through your mind?
Nervous excitement.
What are you nervous about?  I don't
know. it's the unknown isn't it?
But look how gorgeous everyone is.
Beautiful. Everyone is beautiful.
Standing in front of you are three
couples. We have Kendall and Niall.
Hayley and Eyal.
Laura and Wes.  Yep.
We've got two hot single ladies
still: Samira and Dani.
And we've got lovely Alex here
on the subs bench.  All right. Alex.
You can choose to couple up with
any of the girls that you want.
OK. girls. if you fancy Jack.
please step forward.
Girls don't forget if you're in a
couple. you can still step forward.
Dani and Samira have stepped
forward for you.
what do you think?
I was hoping someone would step
forward.  That's all you wanted.
You have got two single girls who
have stepped forward for you.
You can choose any girl you like
standing in front of you.
I think Dani's lovely. I'll couple
up with Dani.
Congratulations. off you go.
You all right?
Nice to meet you.
Samira. don't worry. we have the
lovely Alex on the subs bench.
If you go and join Samira. we have
our fifth couple!
Hey.
So. guys. congratulations.
We have our five couples.
Kendall and Niall.
Hayley and Eyal.
Samira and Alex.
Dani and Jack.
And Laura and Wes.
The choices you've just made
could decide how long you stay
in the villa.
In your couples. you will spend
time getting to know one another.
Taking on challenges together.
living together
and even sharing a bed together.
Sound good?
Too soon to spoon?
Never.
Can I just say. you all make such
lovely-looking couples?
Thank you.
It almost seems a shame to
complicate things.
But this is Love Island.
And here's Adam.
Oh.
Jesus.
Shit.
Hello. Caroline. Are you all right?
Good thank you. Adam. how are you?
Boys. girls.
There's not much left to the
imagination really is there?
I'm Adam. I'm 22 and a personal
trainer.
And I'm from Newcastle.
I get paid to pretty much train
girls which isn't a bad thing
spending time with them
every hour of the day.
I'm definitely not like the serious
person you see on Instagram
with the abs out and all of that.
Not at all.
I've been single now for a few
months.
The biggest thing I bring to
relationship is just having a laugh.
I want to have fun. Three words to
describe me: flamboyant. fun. quick.
So I've got abs. what more
would anyone else want?
Hello. Are you all right?
Boys.
you are looking a bit worried.
(LAUGHTER) Jack?
He's good-looking isn't he?
I mean he is tall. dark
and handsome isn't he?
Samira. is he your type?  Yeah.
Wes. how are you feeling?
I feel like I should have done a
couple more weeks at the gym.
Hayley. is Adam a good-looking man?
Yeah. he's nice. but I'm happy with
who I'm with.
Adam. what do you think of
our girls?
The girls are amazing.
OK. which one is taking your eye?
Number two. I like number two.
Hello. Dani. are you all right?
All right.
Hold on. mate.
There's a couple.
Sorry. I don't know your names.
Guys if you are worried. I don't
blame you because in 24 hours.
Adam will be coupling up with one
of your girls.
leaving one of you single and
vulnerable.
I'm going to leave you lot to get
to know each other and don't forget
in eight weeks' time the public
will be voting
for their favourite couple.
That couple could stand to win a
massive £50.000
and be crowned the winners of Love
Island 2018.
I will see you very soon. bye for
now.
And. Adam. enjoy being single.
Still to come.
Adam's on the prowl...
What I want to know is.
where's your head at?
I'm not going to rule anyone out
right now.
Here in paradise. the villa's
already working its magic
on these lovebirds.
That is literally their first date.
The humans are being
a bit more reserved
but. after the first coupling up
our love matches are...
..and...
Tomorrow. Adam will steal a lady.
but he hasn't talked to one.
cos they've nipped off
for a girly goss.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Yeah. are you?
Wes isn't my usual type. at all.
I just stood forward because...
Is it cos...
You two look like a model couple
together.  Is he your type?
Yeah. he has got like a cute face
and his teeth.
I am actually very happy.
He is so friendly.
That's the best one. I think.
Yeah. he's so funny.
I don't think there's anybody
really that is more my type
than maybe Niall.
So. I'm very happy.
While the girls discuss
potential relationships
over on the Sun Deck. the boys
are comparing their choppers.
Your teeth are absolutely mad.
You're sitting in the sun
and they have this glow.
It is going to be jokes. man.
honestly.
Jesus. they are all standing
there... "Bloody hell!"
I am actually very happy to be
coupled with Jack.
His teeth are really white.
like they are so white.
Don't get me wrong. I'm happy.
we are very good to get on.
I don't mind sharing a bed with him.
What do you do?
I sell office supplies.
I sell pens. mainly.
Sell pens. pads.
If you need paper. pens or pads...
You sell pens? That is brilliant.
I never heard that before.
I don't even know that was a thing.
Trust me. it's a massive thing.
That is brilliant.
Yeah. first impression of Dani is.
she's very pretty. she is really
easy to get on with.
It just dawned on me that Jack
and Dani mean something in Cockney
rhyming slang.
Fanny.
You couldn't write it.
but if you wanted to.
Jack will sort you out
a lovely little biro
and he'll do it for trade price.
Earlier. nobody stepped forward for
Alex and he was sick as a parrot -
and sadly he's not a vet.
How do you feel about it?
I mean. obviously. it wasn't my best
start.
I mean. I didn't get picked.
It's not the start you want. You
have to get on with it.
I don't think it went as well as I
would like to. Not the way I would
want to start my time here.
I have to pick myself up
and get on with it.
So you work in A&E? That's intense.
How long have you been single?  Three
years now.
What about you?  Two years this
summer.  Tell me what you do.
I was in Dream Girls and then Mama
Mia before that.  Entertainment is
covered. We are a power couple!
I think he could be a grower. but to
be with me. I need someone with
a lot of personality.
If he puts a firework up his bum.
I don't know. I need to be with
someone with a lot of energy.
Alex. pull your finger out so Samira
can shove a firework up there.
Hayley and Eyal are getting on.
And there is so much he can teach
her. How do you say your name?
Eyal.  Better. Eyal. E-Y-A-L.
Eyal.  Yeah. without the 'Yal'
at the end. Take it slow.  Eyal.  Yes.
I'm mouthing it with you now.
Do you have a type?
No. I don't know.
Blondes.
And people with beautiful eyes and
someone who I get on with who isn't
too superficial?
What does superficial mean?
Educated.  Someone who doesn't see
past the surface. someone who can
get deep and talk.
I love talking. Are you quite deep?
I'm a deep guy.
I'm feeling confident with Hayley.
I was worried it would be awkward
between me and whoever I was ending
up with. it hasn't been awkward
Guys. that was totes hashtag deep.
Kendall and Niall are
over on the Sun Deck.
or as I call it after the sun's
gone down. the Deck. Deep.
So I was with my ex for five years.
Five?  We had a house. We lived
together. I was engaged.  Marriage?
And then woke up one morning and was
like. he said. "I don't want to be
with you. I want to be with the
lads." I could never do that to a
girl as stunning as you.  Oh. my god.
shut up.  Tell me to rein it in
because I can lay it on too thick.
This is why I stepped forward for
you. You are so confident walking in
and
you are quite loud and funny. I
thought you know what?  You thought I
was funny?  My first impressions are
good. he is so lovely. so it's nice
to have him by my side because he
brings out my fun side.
which I really like. What are your
tattoos of?
OK. I have Hermione Granger's
wand.  Oh. my God. I'm such a Harry
Potter fan.  What's your favourite
film?  Do you know what. I don't like
the first one.
You don't want the Philosopher's
Stone and chill?
I think Kendall is very fit. she
finds me funny. so obviously day
one.
first couple. she gets my sense of
humour. she's fit. I'm living it
now.
What would you have done if I
stepped forward again for someone
else? Would you have pulled me back?
When Adam walked out. I was like...
I think he was a threat to all boys.
though.
I was looking at him. the veins in
his legs just staring at me in the
face. I was like. "Have a day off!"
I'm coming over.  Come to join the
party.  Come join in with your 15
abs.
How are we?  You look good.  What I
want to know is. where your head's
at?
Cos obviously you've got the pick.
Where is your head at?  Every single
girl in here is good-looking. You
all look amazing.
so I'm not going to do anything yet.
You just wanna be out there. or
tell everybody what I'm thinking.
In 24 hours Adam is going to take on
the girls' offers.
I think he has the abs
and the looks. but I think I've got
better chat.
so I feel the chat will win. but I
feel like if you meshed us both. we
would be unstoppable.
How tall are you?
6ft 5in.
I feel sick!
I think I can feel all of the boys
are sweating. I think the next 24
hours will be a lot of fun. For me
anyway.
The girls are about to discover
something very exciting
in the villa. I mean. not
pretend-grass-glued-to-a-wall
exciting. no-one's topping that.
(SCREAMING)
ALL: Oh. my God!
Who's next to me?
You're next to me!
They're lovely.  Yey!
So walking into the bedroom. . that
was the moment
for me when I was like.
"This is actually real."
It will also be so interesting to
sleep with a guy that you just met.
Alex so nice. but he's not my type
at all.
His personality is lovely.
you know what I mean?
I will give him a chance.
completely.
ALL: Yes.
He is a doctor.
I was like what the f...
He's a doctor!
I know. My ex was. as well.
So weird.
So weird. And working in A&E. Alex
has seen some pretty nasty injuries.
but every doctor knows nothing hurts
more than the televised double pie.
When I had a chat. we ended up
dysfunctioning together.
Don't take it to heart. bruv.
It was a double whammy. wasn't it?
First. not getting picked and then
getting that afterwards.
Every day is a new day.
Exactly.
Adam. though... Do you fancy him?
Yeah. I do. I do fancy him.
Laura started with Alex.
Then moved on to Wes
and now she fancies Adam.
Typical air stewardess -
very flighty.
I need to chat to Laura
a bit more to be fair.
I've never had the chance
to sort of get on with her
on a one-to-one basis.
We will get cracking tomorrow.
Are you going to lay it on thick?
What's the plan?
I only know one way and it's thick.
I would like to know
other approaches.
Now. we've got time on our hands.
I think.
I suppose we don't have. actually...
when my man's lurking.
Do you have a bird you proper fancy?
What's your type?
I am completely open. because
I haven't had a chat with someone.
I will just have to steal
one of your birds. haven't I?
As the sun sets on day one. it looks
like Laura's got her eye on Adam.
Wes is going to have to stay
on the case. Or under it.
Squat that!
Whatever works for you. Wes.
Girls. how are you feeling.
first night?  I can't wait.
Check.
Would you kiss him on the first
night?  Not on the first night.
That is so...  No!
I just want to say.
it's our first night
and I really hope
that we all find love
and I'm so glad
to have met you all.
Cheers. guys.
Ladies and gentlemen.
we interrupt this dance montage
with some breaking news.
Reports are coming in that
Samira still does not fancy Alex.
With more on this story.
let's go live to Samira.
Alex is so lovely. he's just not
my type.  Don't beat yourself up
about it. it's day one.  Adam's fit.
But I really like Laura.  At the end
of the day.
he's recoupling in 24 hours.
If you think he's your type. get in.
I kind of fancy
Adam. In the beginning I didn't. it
was weird. But now I fancy him.
What do these girls see
in that 6ft 5in Adonis
with his big brown eyes?
He's younger than you. He's 20. I'm
29. I feel a little bit bad. cos...
He's not my usual type of person.
looks-wise. (LAUGHS) Ohh!
Obviously I feel... Everybody feels
vulnerable with Adam.
It's not comfortable for anyone
who's in a couple.
What is your type?  You mean
looks-wise?
Go. boy. we're behind you.  I don't
know...  Can I have a quick chat?
Let's go to the roof terrace.  I
think the boys are a little bit
intimidated by me. I was speaking to
Laura and Wes came in.
What are your thoughts about Adam?
Looks-wise he is my usual type.
I don't know if it is just looks...
when I was getting in there. we kind
of got interrupted. I would never
chase a guy that didn't like me.
I just wanted to clarify this.
So. head is saying Wes and
heart says Adam - mainly not the
heart. just maybe sexual things.
I've always wanted to do acting.
My dad's an actor.
Having that in my family. it was
weird for me being brought up
with it. My dad's Danny Dyer.
No. he's not!  Yeah. yeah.
I had to bring up my dad.
It was a nice reaction. Boys
get all gangster and start quoting
films.
He didn't and I thought. thank God
for that.
We don't know each other. we're
getting to know each other.
We have been thrown together.
I will probably forget...
He's funny. He is genuine.
I know he sounds pissed.
I'd have to make his job up
if anything happened. I am happy.
Can I have a chat?  Of course.
Oh. no.
When I saw Adam taking Dani for a
chat. I was like. "Oh no."
I have this instant attraction to
Dani. I don't know where it goes.
I can't... With Jack. we really get
on.
I'm happy.
I've only known him a day.
So what if I pick you tomorrow?
If I get picked. I can't cry about
it.
Jack's trying to box her off.
I don't think she wants that to
happen.
She is still playing the game. she
probably it's the safe option.
What about you? What are you
thinking?
Go with someone you want to get to
know.
Who do you want to know the most?  He
clicked on to you. didn't he?
The forbidden fruit.
You're the forbidden fruit!
Maye the banana.
So. will Dani be Adam's
forbidden fruit?
Of course Jack's forbidden fruit
is raspberries.
cos the pips get stuck in his teeth.
And it looks like Adam's not
the only one making his move.
This is actually romantic. I am
taking things at your pace. getting
to know each other. See what
happens.
Oh. my days. No spooning.
It's too soon to spoon? It's never
too soon to spoon!
It's time to hit the hay...
..and we're going eco-friendly
this year.
so bedroom lighting will be provided
by Jack's gnashers.
Are you creaming your whole body in
front of the mirror? I have never
seen a man cream.
You want to play with it?
He's cute.
You look good. You look pretty. I
want to take you on a date.  Take me
on a date?  Ballroom dancing!
# Rhythm of the Night
Adam's determined to make this
the last night he's on his own.
so those boys better be up
for a fight.
I didn't mean that literally. Alex.
you can take the mouthguard out.
Still to come.
Adam turns on the charm.
I fancy you. obviously. you are
beautiful.  Fishing!
It's a brand-new day in paradise.
Play some drums to scare that bird
off!
Thank you.
So. our current couples are...
Samira and Alex.
Laura and Wes.
Kendall and Niall.
Dani and Jack.
And Hayley and Eyal.
As for Adam. later today. he's gonna
be stealing a girl.
Last night. I spoke to Dani and
Laura. they're both lovely girls.
Good morning!
I think it's only fair to go around
and talk to other girls. to make a
fair decision. He is starting with
Samira. I'm going out on a limb now.
but I don't think that girl fancies
Alex.
What was last night like?
With Alex?  Yeah.
He's so shy. He didn't say good
night or anything.
It's hard. isn't it?
Really hard.
She is quite funny. but it was nice
and refreshing.
You have to go through the awkward
conversations and
actually get to know someone. It's
gonna be a mad decision. isn't it?
I'm getting there.  Adam is proper
fit.
You're hot. mate.
This is a mind-fuck.
I don't want to step on people's
toes.  So. this is a bit awkward.
I think we both like Adam. So you do
like him?
I don't like him. I don't know.
He's not mine!
We were having a chat about Adam.
it was all very polite.
I was like. "Damn it. if he
picks her. this is the worst!"
So you don't mind if I speak to him.
No. He's not mine.
It's all going to kick off. I think.
Let the best woman win!
She might not be the best woman. but
she is definitely the fastest.
She made it to the sofa in the space
of a two-second music sting!
What are you thinking?  I don't know.
I literally love yous all in your
own little way.
I don't know know where my head is
right now. All of the girls are
obviously very good-looking.
If I came in. would you step
forward?.
Fishing!  I wasn't!
Yeah. If you go on looks. definitely
yes.
I think she definitely fancies me.
I can't read you.
This is what everyone says.
Straight down the line.
I fancy you. obviously.
You're beautiful. you know
what I mean?
All the girls are beautiful.
I don't envy you. at all.
It's weird. I feel like the whole
Adam thing in his situation.
I think you are thinking about it
way more than me.
It's not even been like an issue
for me. I have been like. "Hm."
He's massive! He is!  Stop!
It's not an issue for me.
I can see the effort he has made
with the other girls
compared to me.
I just think that he thinks that
we are quite tight.
I want to show you all my layers.
Just kind of unravel.
I have really come out of my shell.
That is deep. It is actually deep.
Yeah.
Hello.
Do you mind if I borrow Kendall?
Are you all right?  Yeah. You?
Good. You're getting a tan.
I haven't had the chance to speak to
you.
The vibe between me and Kendall
is going well.
Adam can just do Adam. Like...
It wouldn't be the best move.
More power to him.
If I walked in. would you step
forward?  Obviously.
Would you be bothered if
I said it was you?
I don't know how I'd feel.
Would you be happier?
I am really happy with Niall. I feel
like...
I don't know.
I really get on with him.
It's really weird. I feel like
It feels like home. Already.
I feel really comfortable.
The big dog comes in with his yellow
shorts just like...
Don't be intimidated. He needs to do
what he needs to do.  I am worried.
Imagine a big fat sledgehammer.
That's what he's got.
I've got a little pick-axe.
He can just come in and wallop...
Coming up. decision time!
The time has come for you to choose
which girl you want to couple up
with.
As night falls over the villa.
Adam faces a tough decision.
Do I shampoo AND condition?
I don't even know where my head is
right now.
It's a big decision and it has
consequences.
I've got a nervy belly.
I'm not happy with Alex.
The ideal scenario is that Adam
picks me.
Expect the unexpected.
that's what you say.
I don't fell like he's going to go
for me. so maybe it's Laura.
I'm excited for whoever gets
chosen. We'll see what happens.
If I can put money on it. I think
he'll choose Dani.
I feel a bit sick about it. I don't
want to be that girl.
Inside I'm like.
"What is going to happen?"
Shit's about to go down.
I think he will go for Laura.  I'll
be honest with you. I'm a bit
nervous.
I can't do nothing against Adam.
I'm not holding out.
I am feeling gale-force prangy.
I can't trust a guy in that
kind of shape. You can't.
No boy in this villa wants Adam to
steal their girl. It's that simple.
It is what it is. It's the game.
it's what you've got to do.
Adam is about to stand on someone's
toes. which will break their heart.
And their metatarsal.
(TEXT ALERT)
Got a text!
He's got a text!
What does it say?
Oh. my gosh.
# When I'm here
I need your kindness...
So. obviously. it's not easy to have
to take one of the girls away from
you boys. But I'm sure you would all
do the same in my position.
The decision that I have made
is based on the chats that I've had.
I've tried to get to know all of you
one by one.
The girl that I've decided to couple
up with. I was attracted to her
from when I first saw her.
She fits what I'd be looking for.
the conversations I've had. she's
a good person.
She definitely ticks a lot of boxes
for me.
So the girl I want to couple up with
is...
subtitles by Deluxe
.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today